exports.seed = knex => {
  return knex('questions').insert([
    {
      id: "1",
      question: "Anzac Day is held on?",
      a: "24 April",
      b: "25 April",
      c: "26 April",
      d: "27 April",
      answer: "25 April",
    },
    {
      id: "2",
      question: "The first Anzac Day commemoration occurred in?",
      a: "1915",
      b: "1916",
      c: "1939",
      d: "1990",
      answer: "1916",
    },
    {
      id: "3",
      question: "ANZAC stands for?",
      a: "Australian and New Zealand Army Corps",
      b: "Australian and New Zealand Artillery Company",
      c: "American and New Zealand Army Corps",
      d: "Australian and New Zealand Army Club",
      answer: "Australian and New Zealand Army Corps",

    },
    {
      id: "4",
      question: "A symbol commonly associated with Anzac Day is?",
      a: "A Kiwi",
      b: "A Silver Fern",
      c: "A Red Poppy",
      d: "A Yellow Rose",
      answer: "A Red Poppy",

    },
    {
      id: "5",
      question: "Apart from the poppy what plant holds special significance on Anzac Day?",
      a: "Oregano",
      b: "Rosemary",
      c: "Basil",
      d: "Thyme",
      answer: "Rosemary",
    },
    {
      id: "6",
      question: "What is the Gallipoli Campaign also known as?",
      a: "Battle of Passchendaele",
      b: "Somme Offensive",
      c: "Champagne-Marne",
      d: "Dardanelles Campaign",
      answer: "Dardanelles Campaign",
    },
    {
      id: "7",
      question: "How long did the battle at Gallipoli last?",
      a: "2 months",
      b: "6 months",
      c: "10 months",
      d: "18 months",
      answer: "10 months",
    },
    {
      id: "8",
      question: "Te Papa’s famous Gallipoli exhibition is called what?",
      a: "Gallipoli: The Scale of our War",
      b: "The ANZACs and Gallipoli",
      c: "New Zealand in World War I",
      d: "War and the Aftermath",
      answer: "Gallipoli: The Scale of our War",
    },
    {
      id: "9",
      question: "What is the Last Post?",
      a: "A poem",
      b: "A bugle call",
      c: "A book",
      d: "A campaign",
      answer: "A bugle call",
    },
    {
      id: "10",
      question: "Who wrote the poem For the Fallen (Famous for its fourth stanza that begins with “They shall grow not old, as we that are left grow old”?",
      a: "Edgar Allan Poe",
      b: "John Greenleaf Whittier",
      c: "Laurence Binyon",
      d: "Emily Dickinson",
      answer: "Laurence Binyon",
    },
  ])
}
